The main argument
made in this excerpt is that
and the colouring
in this excerpt is that the coloring of animals is not coincidental.
This excerpt is that the colouring of animals is not coincidental.
and that every animal
is a particular color for a vision. Either the color
is a particular color for a reason. Either the coloring matches with the environment to off.
either the coloring matches with the environment to offer the any more some protection.
Or else, it's somehow support.
the animals behavioural pet.
it somehow supports the animals behavioural patterns.  The idea is musk.
clearly stated by the author in the video.
The idea is most clearly stated by the author in the opening sentence where he says,
The color of animals is...
no
by no means a matter.
chance it depends on many consideration.